# **Henry Moule**

Software Developer Born 1995 in Bristol





# Experience

# **Full Stack Engineer**

SALT

Since Aug 2021

I work for the dating app SALT, as one of two developers, across the MERN (Mongo, Express, React/React Native, Node.js) stack. My focus is on the frontend, primarily on the React Native mobile app, but I do extensive work developing the Node.js backend, internal admin panel (React) and am currently completely rebuilding the website using Next.js.

#### JavaScript Developer

CarePlanner Ltd

Nov 2019 - Aug 2021

At Careplanner, I worked on the then newest iteration of the mobile app, which provides an appointment rostering functionality enabling carers to check in and out of appointments. The app uses React Native and consumes a GraphQL API, provided by AWS AppSync, which links it to the CarePlanner REST API.

## Software Developer

**Active Inspiration Technologies** 

January 2018 - November 2019

For Active Inspiration I primarily worked on the Fuell React Native app, however I also worked across the stack, developing the Fuell backend using Node.js/Parse Server. Active Inspiration had many clients for whom I developed various solutions, using technologies including React, Node.is, GraphQL and Next.js.

#### **Junior Software Developer**

**DYRNAN Communications** 

July 2017 - December 2017

At DYRNAN, I worked primarily on the frontend, using React Native to develop an encrypted messaging app called Secoti (formerly Dyrnan).

#### Freelance Web Developer

**Candour Creative** 

July 2016 - September 2016

Candour Creative outsourced some of their development work to me, which involved developing the website nicksweeney.co.uk using WordPress as a platform to create a custom CMS (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).

#### Support Representative

WebCurl Ltd

November 2014 - June 2016

For my year in industry during my Computer Science degree, I worked for WebCurl, a web development agency based in Oxford, where I helped develop websites using Drupal (PHP, MySQL, JavaScript, CSS).



#### Education

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.) Computer Science at Oxford Brookes University

2013 - 2017

A 4-year course (including a year in industry) covering Java with a focus on OOP and other modules, including Python, C/C++, JavaScript and C#. My

#### About me

Outside of work you'll find me working on various coding projects. I am currently working with a Personal Trainer and Osteopath who commissioned me to develop a fitness/workout app called Christian Antonee Health. I'm also passionate about game development and am teaching myself to build games with the Unity engine and C#.

I have also worked in multiple Agile environments, with experience working with Jira, Asana and Hive.

# Skills



#### Contact

■ Bristol

hen10@hotmail.co.uk

07577635916

🔇 https://moulie415.github.io/portfoli

moulie415

course also involved a teaching module, for which I spent a week as a teaching assistant, helping to teach Python and Scratch at a secondary school. In my final year, as part of my final year project, I developed a maths game called Equation Dragger, that is currently available on the Google Play Store.

### Queen Elizabeth's Hospital

2006 - 2013

A-levels: Mathematics (B), Music Technology (C), Religious Studies (C) GCSEs: 10 GCSEs including an A\* in music and A grades in Maths, History, Biology, Chemistry, Physics and Religious Studies.